Diana Davies Papers, 1960s-1996 (ongoing)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Theatre and Public Art
  - Festivals
    - "Lockup - Lockdown Prison piece - Theatre Thing" 1997, with Diana Davies, street performance, Northampton, MA (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - "Silver Fist of Justice Theatre" economic justice performance piece, Northampton, MA, 1990s (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Hillary Kay - theatre woman, busker, poet - en route to CA. Boston, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Sky Halm - theatre woman; Elizabeth Nutting - painter and theatre woman; Brendon Rule - theatre person, actor, musician - portraits (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - "Waffles - the clown" Social justice street theatre person, 1993. Western Mass (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Guerrilla Girls "No Newt" Action, 1996 (?) (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - "Iguana Sun" Theatre and People's Space - Meredith, founder, Maine, 1993 and Iguana Sun all-around Town Theatre Event (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - "Fertile Mind" kids mask and makeup and face paint workshop, Coastal Maine, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Diana Davies at "Mythweaver's Theatre" event, 1993, Maine. Photo by "Tammy" (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - "Trevor the Games Man" performer, "play-organizer" and stilt-walker. Northampton, MA, 1990s (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Printed matter - cool theatre info (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - The San Francisco Mime Troupe, NYC - on tour, mid 1960s (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - "Comedians against Nukes" (CAN) street theatre (with large imitation nuclear waste-container vehicle) 1998, Northampton, MA (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Revolutionary Anarchist Youth (RAY) theatre action "Anti-Columbus Day" 1995, Northampton, MA (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Dance Theatre
    - Crank-it-out improv. dance theatre at Thornes Market performance space. Letter to Johanna Walker, founder of the Dance Theatre Co. info, 1999. Northampton, MA, DJD has performed with them (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Puppet People
    - Cathi Finney, puppetmaker, puppeteer, theatre woman, activist. Coastal Maine, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Puppet theatre by Michelle S. Wilde, Women's Rights and Spirituality issues. Also "BLO" - "Boobie Liberation Organization" member - about Women's Right to not wear shirts, 1999, at Third Wave Bookstore, Northampton, Mass. (includes Sky Halm, theatre woman) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Clowns, Mimes
    - Sherry Mestel - clown, social justice activist, social worker, theatre woman, editor, publisher, New Brunswick, NY, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Laurie (Louise) Krauth - clown at Sagaris Feminist Institute, 1975, Lyndonville, VT (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Chris Yerlig "Hoopoe the Clowne" mime and street theatre and show performer, Northampton, MA, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Chris Yerlig, "Hoopoe the Clowne" street performance, Northampton, MA, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Theatre People and Performance Artists
    - Theatre woman and Social Justice Activist Carol "Kali" Grosberg, and "Apple" the cat, 1973, NY state (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Bern Porter - writer, publisher, performance artist-80th birthday celebration theater event, 1991, Maine (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Pat Styer - theatre woman and street busker. Victoria theatre - old Vaudville palace - Greenfield, MA, 1993. Vaudville props display (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Stephen Baird, street theatre, busker, founder - street artists' guild, Mass, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Neil Alan - "Mr. NK Lean Young" theatre and film shoot, 1996, Northampton, MA (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Linda Garson-Smith, actor, teacher, Belfast Maskers' Theatre performance, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Diana Sands, actor, 1965. Town Hall, NYC (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Sidney Poitier, France Nuyen, Robert Culp, actors, 1968 - at the poor people's march (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Viveca Lindfors, actor, 1967 - on the Jeannette Rankin Brigade peace march, Washington DC (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Circus
    - Molly Pelley, clown, at Circus Smirkus, Putney VT, 1994, on tour (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Clyde Beatty and Cole Bros. Circus on tour, NY state, 1985. - girls watching tigers in cage (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous color slides - circus, street festivals, theatre, fairs, carnivals, clowns, various locations and dates (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Coney Island (NY) circus theatre sideshow, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Play Script and Papers
    - The War Machine - a play by Diana Davies (1998) - script and production notes, flyers - Radical Arts Theatre (RAT) (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - A Riot of Colour For Manny Shirazi (2001) a play by Diana Davies - script and production notes, flyers (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - The Soup-Tin Garden (2001) a tiny play by Diana Davies - script, production notes, flyers (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Dance
  - The Dance Book. Miscellaneous bits from an info scrapbook on things moving (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - From the Dance Center at East. St., Hadley, MA, Jan. 2000. Performances by The Dance Generators - with Amie Dowling, founder and choreographer - dancer (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Crank-it-out: Dance theatre performances (annual) by this divers group. This one, 1999 (includes Jennifer Polins, Maggie Shollenberger, Lani Nahele (Lisa Schmidt), Johanna Walker, Francis Savage Saliq and Jeff Bliss) (ongoing events) Northampton, MA (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Capoeira Angola. Dance and Martial arts form, at a theatre and street festival, Belfast, Maine, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Dancers at "Sankofa" street festival. Belfast, Maine, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Women's Flamenco and archaic dance form class. Boston, early 1980s (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Cuban folk dancers, Havana, Cuba, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Girls dancing in a park at outdoor music festival, 1969, Washington DC (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "Circle Dance," men dancing around fountain, Washington Square Park, NYC, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Man dancing in fountain, Lincoln Center, NYC, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Graffiti - "If I can't dance, then I don't want to be part of yr revolution" on Railroad trestle. Northampton MA, Apr. 2001 (Emma Goldman Quote) (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Street Artists, Musicians and Buskers and Craftspeople: The Busker Book (a travelling scrapbook of Buskers)
  - Street performers, 1960s and 1970s, NYC, Philadelphia, Boston (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Buskers, Western Mass and Portland, Maine, Coastal Maine, 1980s-current (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Buskers, Portland, Maine and Western Mass.,1980s-on (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Mimes and musicians, Western Mass, 1980s-1990s (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Info and article, "The War Against Street Artists" by Diana Davies, performers' licenses, song, clippings, 1997-on (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous color slides of street artists and miscellaneous info and cross-referenced b&w (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Diana Davies, Pat Styer, and Kady playing street music, 1992, Northampton, MA. Photos by Amy Greene (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Diana Davies and Kady playing music on the street 1991, Northampton, MA. Photos by Pat Styer (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Heather Kahn, Fiddler and onlookers, old port area. Karl Bergdahl, harmonica. Portland, ME, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Blind Buskers in subway and streets, NYC, 1965. And children, market, miscellaneous street scenes (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "Big WAH Scratch Band" Street musicians - Jug band type - Shelburne Falls - Buckland, Mass, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Street poet, NYC, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Man with flute, on stoop, Lower East side, NY, 1970. Musicians on Sixth Ave. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - The Street Opera Singer, Lower East Side, NYC, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Old man with saxophone and old man with Mandolin - middle of 75th St., West Side, NYC 1969 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Traveling jazz musicians with sculpture and "love" graffiti. Cooper Sq, NYC, 1970 (in street) (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Jazz trio, Main Street, Northampton, Mass, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Rockin' Dave Morash, Cajun Accordianist, 1987, Northampton, Mass. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - "B.C." street busker and jugglers, Pulaski Park, Northampton, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Woman street fiddler, 1985, Northampton, MA (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Mummers, 1999, winter. Northampton, Mass (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Margaret Garrett, street busker from Boston, playing on Northampton Main St., 1998 - being chased away by cop (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - "The Drunk Stuntmen"-1995 playing on street. Northampton, Mass playing (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Diane Sanabria, banjo player and singer - songwriter 1997, Northampton, Mass, street (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Steel drum player Mentos Alwyn, Northampton, Mass street, 1990s (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Gerard Evans, Saxophonist, in Harvard Sq., Cambridge, Mass, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Salamander crossing - Bluegrass/Blues/Rock/Folk Band, 1994. Amherst, Mass street (includes Rani Arbo) (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Street drummers, 1995, Portland, Maine (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Street artists and craftspersons, 1973. Washington Square and Greenwich Village, NYC (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Kady, craftswoman, selling her silver work on the street, 1970s. Various locations (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Musicians Tom Strum and Ned Masengill. Northampton, MA, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - David Bartlett, fiddle. Mark Weinstein, one-man-band, Northampton, MA, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Lyndon Engle, Steve Robillard, Kip Morris - blues and folk music - Northampton St, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Jeremy Keith, from Ireland, playing Bouzouki with his Irish music, 1996, Northampton, MA (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Bus station bass player, 1995. Springfield, MA (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - African - American, street drummers, 1995, Philadelphia (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Musicians: Ar Adler and Linda Webb, 1960s. Sixth Ave, New York City (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Printed matter on street musicians, miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Women and Music
  - Women musicians, miscellaneous (includes cross-reference material) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Betty Carter, jazz singer and arranger, 1970s (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Carmen McRae, jazz singer, Village Gate, NYC, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Dorothy Donegan, jazz musician, 1980s, Boston area (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Bougainvillea. A women's jazz band and Dorothy Donegan (band includes Jeannette Muzima, vibes player and composer) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Lena Horne, 1967 - singer - in NYC (no negatives) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Juanita Hall - jazz, blues, Broadway show singer, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Alberta Hunter, 1978 - blues-jazz singer, at NYC Cabaret: "The Cookery" (and poster of her) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Nancy Wilson, pop and jazz singer, 1966 at NYC Cabaret: "Royal Box" (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Rashida Shah, jazz singer, Boston, Mass, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Streisand, 1968, NYC. Opening night of "Funny Girl" singer, actress, movie producer (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Joan Armatrading - rock musician, songwriter, 1977 in Portland, Maine (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Joan Baez - musician, songwriter, activist, various dates (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Joan Jett - rock-punk musician, 1996. Northampton, Mass (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - The Indigo Girls and Mary Chapin Carpenter, Newport Folk Festival, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Micki Metts - rock bassist, songwriter, musician, with band "Diabolix" 1993 in Portland, Maine (one of the few African-American "punk" or "metal" musicians) (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Barbara Keith - musician, rock songwriter 1990s. Western Mass (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - "Grrrls Rock" the loud festival, Northampton, Mass, 1995 (includes "The Brood, Shiva Speedway, Lori Martin) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Zoë Lewis and Kate Wolf (NOT the folksinger with same name) - "The Rubber Band" 1995, Green River Café, Greenfield, Mass. (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Zoë Lewis at "The Taste of Northampton" at Smith College, and Iron Horse Music Hall, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Aimee Swift and Zoë Lewis - musicians, at Hampshire College Women's "Wow" music festival, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Aimee Swift and Amy Greene - rock musicians, songwriters, record company founders, band members, "Pirate Jenny" band. "Red Hot Records" Record Co., 1990s, Western Mass, photos, recording, and info (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Amy Greene - musician, band member, flutist, songwriter, arranger, composer, 1992, at Smith College (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Lyn Haney - songwriter, musician, NYC 1970 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Judy Ricardi, Worcester, Mass 1995. Producer of Women's Rock music shows, radio broadcasts and events. Also: music critic, D.J. and publisher (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Michelle Shocked - musician, songwriter, at the Northampton Brewery, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Cindy Bow - musician, songwriter, 1990s, Western Mass (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - "Women Rock" - musicians - Jen Gallahorn, Aimee Swift, Cindy Bow and "Ellen James Society" band, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Women musicians - Jamming with friends. Miscellaneous, varied dates (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Rock for Choice - benefit rock show for Women's rights group, Portland, Maine, 1990s (Women's Rock bands playing for this National org.) (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Mimi Verlaine, 1976. Musician, guitarist, NY State (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Gospel singer, Rhode Island, mid-1960s (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Sara Pirtle - folk musician, and performer and storyteller for children, writer, 1994. Benefit for "Swords into Plowshares" the Western Mass pacifist org. (Includes Pete Seeger, Tao Rodriguez-Seeger, in background) Northfield - Mt Hermon (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Diana Davies, miscellaneous Music matter. Flyers, posters, songs, photos, what-not- music by - and- as played by Diana Jo (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Women's Music
  - Musicians and women's music scene, miscellaneous includes - Teresa Trull (1975), Willie Tyson (1977), Martha Siegel (cellist, 1976), and some printed - published material (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Marilyn Ries - one of the first women sound engineers 1975 and 1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Boston Women's Music Festival, Sanders Theatre, Harvard Univ. Includes - Mary Watkins, Hazel Dickens, C.T. and April, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Allegra" women's music production co., Boston Mass, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous color slides, includes - Margie Adam, Meg Christian, Willie Tyson, "Isis" Rock Band, Alix Dobkin, Holly Near, Kay Gardner (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - New England Women's Symphony (NEWS), Boston, 1979-1980, includes - Kay Gardner, Nan H. Washburn (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - New England Women's Symphony (NEWS) (includes K. Gardner), 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Kay Gardner - rehearsals and recording session. Photos for her "Emerging" album, 1970s. Revere, Mass (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Antonia Brico, the conductor, NYC and U of Illinois, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Kay Gardner, Betty MacDonald, Gwen Avery, Robin Fre, Robin Flower, Mary Watkins-1970s-1980s. Performances and jams (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - "Mojo" flute player, performer and feminist-activist. Teddy Hold (a woman) - musician and songwriter, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Michigan Women's Music Festival, 1976 and 1977 (includes Gwen Avery, Kady - selling crafts, Betty MacDonald, Holly Near, Teresa Trull, audience, Baba Yaga Jazz Band, Margie Adam, Ginni Clemons, Willie Tyson, Marilyn Ries) (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Women's Music, miscellaneous (includes Meg Christian, Ginni Clemons, Barbara Cobb, Eileen Kane, Betty McDonald, June Millington, Holly Near, Teresa Trull, Trish Williams, Chris Williamson), 1975-76, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Michigan Women's Music Festival (includes Margie Adam, Baba Yaga, Meg Christian, Carol Clement, Ginni Clemons, Maxine Feldman, Jerene Jackson, Holly Near, Linda Tillery, Teresa Trull, Willie Tyson, Andrea Weltman), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Michigan Women's Music Festival (includes Margie Adam, Gwen Avery, Ginni Clemons, Casse Culver, Robin Flower, Kay Gardner, Betty McDonald, Jan Oxenberg, Sally Piano, Sweet Honey in the Rock, Teresa Trull, Willie Tyson), 1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - National Women's Music Festival, University of Illinois, Champaign-Urbana (includes Antonia Brico, Roberta Kosse, Linda Tillery, Jeannie G. Pool, Kay Gardner, Sharon Isbin, Bessie Jones, Ginni Clemons, and jugglers; rehearsals and performances 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Artists, Craftspeople, Architects, Photographers, Videographers, Filmmakers, Actors (film)
  - Artists - Craftspeople
    - Kady - arts and crafts studios. Various locations-1970s-2000s (includes filmmaker-artists Carol Clement and Ariel Dougherty) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Artist-activist Constance "Connie" Trowbridge, 1992. Cambridge, Mass (includes Diana Davies) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Artists Bea Kreloff, 1971, NYC (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Artist Ellen Sperling and her soft-fabric sculpture, 1983, Boston area (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Mary Hynes, artist-craftswoman and her loom and cat, 1996. Wendell, Mass (includes Kady and Pat Styer) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Laura Kaye, painter, Western Mass, 1985 and 1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Paula Gottlieb, artist, Western Mass 1983 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Cybèle Collins, artist, 1996. Western Mass (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Deidre Scherer, fabric artist, 1998. Springfield Museum of Art show, Western Mass (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Alison Berard-Rector, 1993, painter, Maine (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Lucy Carver, artist, 1993, Maine (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Michaela Griffo, artist, NYC, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Sheila Pepe, artist, 1980s and 1990s. Western Mass and her soft sculpture (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Alexander Calder, sculptor, 1960s. NYC (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Artists assorted: Fumio Yoshimura, Wolfgang Flor, Eli Ilan, Kate Sorensen, artist. 1995, Philly (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Architects
    - Randal Korman, architect and sculptor, 1972, NYC (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Photographers
    - Jill Freedman, photographer, 1970, NYC (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Consuelo "Connie" Kanaga, photographer, NY State, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Iris Greenberg, photographer, 1976, NY State (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Photographers, miscellaneous (includes Heather Curtis, Tia Cross, Jeanne Garrison, Nancy Flowers, Heidi Reijm, Peggy McKenna, Joe Alper, John Goodwin, Jaques Charlas, Minoru ("Mickey") Aoki, Jonathan Gaines.), various dates/locations (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Photographer - filmmaker
    - Francine Winham, photographer and filmmaker, London, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Filmmakers
    - Jane Lourie, filmmaker, NYC 1969 and 1970s (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Jane Picard, filmmaker and actor, 1980s. Boston and Western Mass (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Michelle Gisser, video artist and filmmaker, 1983, Western Mass (includes Jeannette Muzima, jazz musician) (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Filmmakers, miscellaneous - cross-reference file and info (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Film Stills
    - Still photos for "Artemesia" a film by Carol Clement and Ariel Dougherty, 1977 (includes photos of filmmakers) and info, "Women Make Movies" organization (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Film stills and work by Diana Davies. Various dates (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Actors, film
    - Marlon Brando, actor, supporting Native American rights movement, 1960s, Washington D.C. (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Actors and Rita Tushyingham, Sophia Loren, Omar Sharif. Director, David Lean, 1965, NYC (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Actor, comic, filmmaker - Woody Allen, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Actors, film, television: Hal Holbrook, Michael J. Pollard, Michael Caine, Martha Raye, and cross-referenced matter (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Videomakers
    - Video woman Phyllis of Amherst (public access) cable TV, April 2001, Amherst, Mass. (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Writers
  - Gwendolyn Brooks, poet at Smith College, Neilson Library, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Deming, 1970s and 1980s, NY State (includes Jane Gapen Verlaine, artist and Consuelo Kanaga, photographer) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Barbara Deming, 1973-78, NY State, NYC (includes Kady, artist-activist- craftswoman) and info (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Beatrice Hawley, poet, activist, co-founder Alice James Press and Common Stock Café. Boston area, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Barbara Smith, writer, editor, essayist, 1980. Boson (includes Tia Cross, photographer) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Women writers read and meet at Sagaris Feminist Institute, Vermont, 1975 (includes Kady, Yvonne Matthews Klein, Margaret Fiedler, Joan Peters) (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Women writers reading for social justice = Grace Paley, Marge Piercy, Denise Levertov, Karen Lindsey, 1980, Cambridge, Mass, at old Cambridge Baptist Church (OCBC) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Kady and Pat Styer, working on and reading their feminist writings, 1991, Western Mass (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Writers - miscellaneous color slides, includes Adrienne Rich, Robin Morgan, Leah Fritz, Blanche McCary Boyd, Honor Moore, NYC, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Grace Paley at "Stop the Draft" rally, NY, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Grace Paley and writer Sybil Claibourne, 1970, NY State (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Grace Paley and Dragon Puppet at peace march, NYC, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Grace Paley with writers Bob Nichols and Paul Johnson, 1976, Vermont (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Grace Paley and writer Robert Nichols (her husband) reading at the Green River Café, Greenfield, Mass, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Denise Levertov, cross-referenced miscellaneous material. 1967 and 1980 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Frances "Fran" Goldin, radical literary agent and people's rights activist, 1971 (cross-referenced material) (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Elena Poniatowska - writer, historian, human rights activist from Mexico. Reading-speaking at Mt. Holyoke College, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Nancy Kelly - writer, editor, professor, feminist literary historian - activist. Western Mass, July 1991 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Nancy Kelly and Elizabeth Lambert, writers, editors, women's literary historians. Western Mass, July 1991 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Nancy Kelly and Mary Daly, 1989. Northampton, Mass. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Mary Daly - speaking/reading. Various dates, NY State and Western Mass (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Mary Daly and her cat friends - "Familiars" 1983, Western Mass. (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - May Sarton, 1980s, NYC. Reading and book signing (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Susan Sontag and writer Paul Blackburn - Angry Arts against the war in Vietnam reading. 1967, NYC (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Alma Routsong (a.k.a. "Isabel Miller") writer, 1971, NYC (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Sue Grafton - mystery novelist, at Odyssey Books. So. Hadley, Mass, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Kate Millett, 1970s. Various locations (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Lucy Parsons Books - radical independent collectively owned bookstore and community space. Central Sq., Cambridge, Mass.,1995 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Writers, miscellaneous: Marty Jezer, Benjamin Spock, David Halberstam, Jean Genet. 1960s-1970s - color slides (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Chinva Achebe - Biafran (now Nigeria) writer. Harvey Swados, writer and essayist, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Herbert ("Herb") Gold, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Dwight MacDonald, Robert Lowell, Stanley Diamond at "End the War Against Biafra," 1969. U.N. Plaza, NYC (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Writers, miscellaneous: Benjamin Spock, Robert Nichols, Jimmy Breslin, Paul Krassner, various dates (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Allen Ginsberg, Peter Orlovsky - poets at an anti-war rally, 1966. NYC (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Allen Ginsberg reading anti-war poems and chanting. NYC, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Allen Ginsberg at a theatre and music event, NYC, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Norman Mailer ["How-to-attack-your-wife-and-be-praised-as-a-famous-writer-old boys-club"] NYC, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Jean Genet - French playwright and writer, 1970. NYC (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Leslie Fiedler, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- The Railroads, Hoboes and Subways
  - Hoboes